{
    "subject": "resource/Carine_Roitfeld",
    "predicate": "ontology/employer",
    "object": "resource/Hearst_Corporation",
    "human_readable": "Carine Roitfeld works for Hearst Corporation.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.867469072341919,
            "question": "What company does Carine Roitfeld work for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8575696349143982,
            "question": "Who works for Hearst Corporation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6770612001419067,
            "question": "Is Carine Roitfeld employed by a media company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6716575622558594,
            "question": "In what industry does Hearst Corporation operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.608465850353241,
            "question": "Has Carine Roitfeld worked in the fashion industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.420662522315979,
            "question": "Can you name a well-known publication associated with Hearst Corporation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.414855420589447,
            "question": "What is Carine Roitfeld's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3637910485267639,
            "question": "What are some of Hearst Corporation's notable publications?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28322508931159973,
            "question": "Is Carine Roitfeld involved in the media world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27247482538223267,
            "question": "Does Hearst Corporation own any magazines?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carine Roitfeld works for Hearst Corporation.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7633_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Carine Roitfeld involved in the media world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7633_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Hearst Corporation's notable publications?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7633_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Carine Roitfeld's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7633_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7633_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7633_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7633_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7633_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7633_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7633_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7633_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7633_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7633_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7633_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Carine Roitfeld's career, including her role as global fashion director of Harper's Bazaar and her association with Hearst Magazines. It also mentions that Hearst will host her CR Fashion Book\u2019s Website and be in charge of its social media. This suggests that Carine Roitfeld works with Hearst Corporation, which is a subsidiary of Hearst Magazines, making the statement \"Carine Roitfeld works for Hearst Corporation\" supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Carine Roitfeld has multiple roles and partnerships with Hearst Corporation. Specifically, she is the global fashion director of Harper's Bazaar (which is owned by Hearst Corp.), CR Fashion Book also works under agreements with Hearst Magazines, and there are mentions of Hearst managing digital content for CRFashionBook.com. These pieces of information support that Carine Roitfeld indeed works for or has significant roles associated with the Hearst Corporation."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}